

JOSHUA GAMIAO

Software Engineer

About Me

I am a skilled full-stack developer with experience in Nuxt.js,
TypeScript, and ReactTS. I excel in converting legacy systems and building eCommerce platforms, focusing on enhancing user experience and system efficiency.

I thrive in collaborative environments and am dedicated to continuous learning.



(63+) 917 153 2102



jgamiao0221@gmail.com



Binan, Laguna, Philippines

LANGUAGE

- English
- Japanese (basic)

SKILLS

Front-End Development:

- Nuxt.js
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS

EXPERIENCE

Associate Research and Development Engineer -Advanced World Solutions Inc. -Makati, Philippines -2022 - 2024

Converted a property management desktop application from C# .Net and Java to ReactTS and ExpressTS. Developed and maintained core frameworks and utilities for over 500 screens and 800 APIs. Responsibilities included module investigation, bug fixing, implementing requirements from Japanese design documents, automated unit testing, and code reviews. Worked as a full-stack developer in collaboration with the internal PH team.

Software Engineer -Narnoo Inc -Brisbane, Australia -2024 - Present

Currently working with this company, focusing on developing an eCommerce platform for booking leisure activities and hotel accommodations. Led both front-end and back-end development using Nuxt.js and TypeScript to ensure a seamless user experience and robust booking system.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2018 - 2022

University of Perpetual Help System Laguna

Back-End Development:

- Nuxt.js
- TypeScript
- Node.js
- Express.js

Database Management:

- MySQL
- SQLite
- MSSQL

Version Control:

- Git
- GitHub
- GitLab

Development Tools:

- Visual Studio
- Visual Studio Code
- Eclipse
- Turbo C
- PyCharm

Testing & Debugging:

- Postman
- Mocha & Chai
- SonarQube

Project Management:

- Redmine
- Asana

Operating Systems:

Windows

CERTIFICATES

- <u>JSE</u>
- Back-end
- Front-end
- Java
- Java Springboot
- Javascript OOP
- MySQL
- <u>Unit Testing</u>